Now everybody lift your hands up!
Sing about what you are dreaming!
Always stand up!
Raise up the flag that can't be beaten!
Gotta keep up!
We'll get past every wall that's
in our wake, go without hesitation!
Hands up!
We just have to press on a little more.
To get to the answers we're looking for.
We came to this new world
believing that surely someday.
We just might find the way.
All the pieces of our dreams
have now come together.
Our bonds won't waver.
With our dreaming hand.
Let's head on towards.
A bright new future.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on never stopping.
Only look up.
Keep your head up way up high.
Always step up.
If waves are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up.
Our wishes, they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
We drift on riding the waves.
Towards another shore day by day.
There are many meetings, many goodbyes.
Underneath the flag we fly.
I'll remember the pain within.
I'll keep it in my heart forever.
And never take it lightly.
But I won't surrender.
This freedom I will keep in mind.
I'll keep holding on, never stop it.
Now everybody lift your hands up.
Sing about what you are dreaming.
Always stand up.
Raise up the flag that you believe in.
Gotta keep up.
We'll get past everyone that's in our way.
Let's head on, never stop it.
Only look up, keep your
head up, way up high.
Always step up, if brains
are rough, jump to the sky.
Never give up, our wishes,
they will come together.
And lead us on for the future.
Hands up.
Momonosuke?
Indeed, that is my name
I swear I've heard that somewhere
before That's really gonna
bug me I can assure you we've
never met before But that aside,
stop staring
And don't drool
You will never make a
snack out of me If you try,
I will swallow you whole Please step away
are you stuck on this thing somewhere
you're talking with your farts right
hey hello what have you lost your mind
you're not a dragon you're a talking eel
wipe away that drool i am not an eel
looks like we're both hungry huh
don't be absurd I am a
proud samurai warrior
ten days of fasting is nothing to me tell
me who are you and why are you here oh me
Lucy I'm gonna be king
of the pirates someday
that's a joke pirates are all white of
girth quite tall in stature hairy and Crude,
their king, would surely smell
much worse than you as well.
Anyway, can you get me out?
Come on, eel.
This is your home, isn't it?
Her name's Momonosuke!
I see.
So you must not be from here either.
I am an outsider as well.
I only know that sick children
have been gathered in this place.
I know not what manner of island this is,
nor what strange fate has befallen me.
My misfortune began when I was discovered
as a stowaway on a
sea-faring vessel nearby.
At first, I tried to distance
myself from the other children here.
But they were so kind, and they
were quite insistent as well.
They're giving out food.
Aren't you hungry?
Heed this!
I am a samurai!
I do not accept alms or pity!
I was terribly stressed.
I do regret my brusqueness.
Don't be shy.
We've got plenty.
I told you I don't want any, didn't I?
But you have to eat something.
We're all separated from our parents,
so we have to stick together.
My turmoil is mine alone!
You do not know how I feel!
Hello, children.
I am Master Caesar.
This room is all yours,
and as long as you're here,
we'll take very special care of you.
Hey, you okay?
What's your name, kid?
I have none for the likes of you.
You hungry?
Here, have a snack.
I don't want it. Candy? Go away!
So you're telling me one
of the children ran away?
Yeah, but it's weird.
Everyone on the boarding
list is accounted for.
That is weird.
Doesn't matter.
Let's just split up and find them quick.
Hey, you!
Momonosuke?
That's an interesting name.
This is a secret room.
It's bad to come here.
You need not involve
yourself with me any further.
Please go away.
You cannot be my friend
because... because I...
I am going to escape this place.
It's sad, but we all know how you feel.
Because we are the same way.
Everyone wants to see their family.
We all want to go home soon.
Even though we all came from
different islands, we're friends now.
And hey, we'll all get better, I'm sure.
In the meantime, even if we miss our
parents, it's not so bad if you ask me.
The biscuit room is so fun.
And we still have each
other to count on, right?
Come back, have something to eat.
Do that, and I'm sure you're going to
feel much better in no time, Momonosuke.
But I, uh...
This door isn't supposed to be open.
Somebody in here?
That's weird.
What did we walk into? No clue.
What happened to Momonosuke?
I think they were storing some
weird Devil Fruit in here.
Dr.
Vegabum tried creating one himself.
I heard it was a failure, though.
Me too, but he made something here.
So, I was a human, once at least.
I see.
So you ate a Devil Fruit?
Well, no biggie.
Why don't you just use your
power to turn back to normal?
What?
It's really that simple?
So I can do that?
Teach me how!
Sorry. I can't.
I don't have Snow powers, you know?
Man, I can't even see
the hole I fell through.
How high does that ceiling go up, anyway?
I am eager to escape this place as well.
The children must be
informed of the truth.
I heard something dreadful.
Caesar, he unwittingly
revealed a dark secret.
Yes, the children are quite obedient.
They're enlarging with no
particular side effects.
But of course,
I don't expect that to last
long since the purpose of
this experiment is to test
the limits of dosage size.
Well, at any rate, I'm sure they'll
all die off in about five years or so.
Hopefully no one will catch on
and we can bring in a new batch.
That man's kindness is
nothing but a facade.
He will drive those children to an early
grave without even an ounce of regret,
and they know nothing.
In truth,
I was already on my way to warn
them of their present danger,
but when I hid in a trash can, I
fell down to this wretched place.
Caesar!
All right, Momo.
We're wasting too much time in here.
I'm getting us out. How?
You remarked yourself on
the height of the ceiling.
I'm gonna climb.
Hold on to my back.
And don't worry about the
kids. They'll be fine.
My friends are on their way to help them.
Is that true?
Yeah, and they always keep their word.
Just worry about yourself for now.
I see.
I was right after all.
You are no lonely pirate, but a valiant.
Momo, do you need food?
Come on, buddy, get up.
You gotta pull it together, okay?
Pull it together.
Oh, cool.
So you can fly.
I hope Nami's team's
doing okay without me.
I mean, they got Zoro, but
he's no Usopp. Hey, Brook!
Look around for some
C-PRISM stone handcuffs!
Robin's ever gonna need them!
Just count on me!
One Samurai-san and a
few pair of handcuffs.
I would imagine both of them
must be somewhere close by.
Let's just slip through this wall first.
Shit!
Everybody, this way!
Just a little bit more!
Head straight into the biscuit room!
That's all it's getting!
Stop complaining!
We're trying our best!
Well, try harder, okay?
Get your ass to the biscuit room now!
We've got some kids to save!
It's cold!
This whole room is a blizzard!
As soon as I take my coat off,
that burp woman makes it slow!
I am gonna choke her!
Stop!
You guys can't eat that
candy no matter what!
Run away, Mocha! Go!
Just give us the candy!
You can't run forever, you know!
You're crazy!
All of this just for candy?
You just want it for yourself!
Don't be greedy!
Perhaps I can slow them down.
I'd rather you not.
Open!
You three, do something
to stop those kids.
You're a Logia type, huh?
All right, then.
Bring it on.
Calvin. Are you OK?
I'll be fine.
It was only a scratch.
But we had better hurry
and stop the children.
You're right.
Oh no, they're leaving!
We can't let the kids get away!
Wait, Mocha!
I promised Mocha I would hold them
off so she could get a head start,
but this has all gone wrong!
I put her in danger!
Look at that candy!
I'm sorry, guys!
Now the choppers tell
me what this stuff does!
I can't let you have it!
Why can't you see that
this candy's hurting you?
Just look what it's making you do!
Mock, we just don't have any choice.
They said we were both really sick.
Mommy! Daddy!
I'm sorry, but you can't see them anymore.
I still wish I could have said goodbye,
but I don't want anything
bad to happen to our parents.
But it's okay.
They said we'd be better in
a year, so let's be brave.
You have no reason to fear.
Whatever it takes, I promise I'll
have all of you sweet children
feeling better in no time.
The truth is, I lost my only
son to this deadly disease.
It broke my heart.
I'll do everything in my power to ensure
no child ever suffers from It again,
and I can't bear to see another
parent bury their precious child.
The way I had to.
Oh, I'm sorry, please excuse me.
I, I shouldn't cry in front of you?
Are you okay, poor master!
Thank you, dear, so kind of you to ask.
Well, anyway, I suppose I should
introduce you to everyone.
These children come from different islands,
but they all share the same ailment.
I'm Uzu.
Nice to meet you.
Candy!
Hi, I'm Dolan.
Come back!
Oh, God!
My name's Gonbe.
We need more candy!
We've got some new friends
joining us today, children.
All right, kids.
Be sure to play nice.
Oh, and let me know if
you need any help, okay?
Okay!
Thanks for days!
Lone seemed so nice, but she tricked us!
Everything she told us was a lie!
You handled your treatment so well.
Have this.
It's a piece of candy from the Master.
Guys, we gotta get out of here!
Hurry up!
Come on, step out of it!
We have to catch up with
the children, and quick!
Let's go!
Hey! Huh?
You really think you can just run away?
Saru, what are you doing?
Don't you dare try to get me!
What is wrong with you?
You can't just use me as a shield!
That's too bad.
Why are you attacking them?
They're no threat to you.
Get out of the way, Zoro.
Heat egg!
I figured melting her would work.
There's more where that
came from, BirdBrain!
So she's the one worth 16 million.
Hey, enough hiding in the snow!
You want to finish this or
not, you oversized chicken?
Look at the door! What's happening?
Snow fence.
No!
Nami, no!
I can't move!
I'm freezing up!
Not again!
Don't let her get you!
All right, Katorea Manos!
Face!
Mommy!
She's so scary!
Sorry, but Master Caesar needs those
test subjects for an important project.
That's why it's my job, to ensure
he and the experiment are kept safe.
But now you've given Mocha
these rebellious ideas. Us!
They chose to leave this awful
place of their own free will!
That's enough!
Out of my way!
Go on, hurry up!
Follow me! Right!
Hang in there, Mocha!
We're on our way!
That's not very nice.
Since the first day they came
to live on the island with us,
We've treated those children with every
comfort and kindness they could ever want.
And yet you're trying
to steal these beloved
treasures from their
adoring foster parents.
But I suppose you are pirates.
If you expect it, then
you must be fine with it.
I told you it's not nice.
You're done interfering.
Sword snow!
Skin sword technique!
You know, I've noticed that all you've
been doing is defending yourself.
So is there some reason why you
haven't tried to attack me at all?
That's funny at first; I thought
there was no way I could defeat you.
How about that?
I guess I was mistaken—there's
another room back here.
Find the children and get
them out as fast as you can.
can It feels like a snowstorm in here.
The Navy.
Come on, let's bust the door open.
It doesn't matter how many of you
come to take those children away.
I'll stop you.
Save those kids!
Why are all those
marines answering to you?
They're not here.
The only person I can see
is pirate hunter Zoro.
Of course that pain in the ass is here.
All right, here's the plan.
Everybody make dumb faces at Mosshead!
I hope they all slip on the ice
and crack their stupid skulls open.
Jackass, Nami and Robin
already went that way.
Why don't you go chase them down? Gotcha!
I knew you would be useful to me one day!
You heard him, boys!
Let's go find the...
Never mind, we've got
a honey right in here!
Take those tail betters! Oh, come on!
Put your jaws up off the floor, morons!
Wait, just look at her, though.
She's half woman, half bird.
No way.
A real-life harpy. Huh?
Yeah, but hey.
Human or not, she sure is a looker, right?
Sexiest bird I've ever seen.
Yeah, I could be into that.
Woo-hoo!
Call me crazy, but I think
you're actually enjoying this.
Hey, why is it snowing?
Are we inside?
It's my duty, after all.
I don't care who you are.
It'll be a cold day in hell when
I let you take those children.
It's my shoulder!
She bit it off!
You'll pay for that!
She's a Nokia-type!
Damn it, woman.
Someone is using Haki on me.
Captain Seagy!
We sealed off the doors to keep the
gas from getting into this room.
But we don't know that it won't
leak in from another spot.
We don't have much time, so do whatever
it takes and rescue all of the children!
What?
But what about you?
I'm going to stay right here.
If you ask me, you could
use a little help here.
What?